Truth is stranger than legend...
Atari: Game Over is a documentary film directed by Zak Penn.
The Xbox Originals documentary that chronicles the fall of the Atari Corporation through the lens of one of the biggest mysteries
of all time, dubbed “The Great Video Game Burial of 1983.” Rumor claims that millions of returned and unsold E.T.
cartridges were buried in the desert, but what really happened there?
Self, played by Nolan Bushnell.
Self, played by Howard Scott Warshaw.
Self, played by Manny Gerard.
Self, played by Joe Lewandowski.
Self, played by Paul Sanchez.
Self, played by Ernest Cline.
Atari: Game Over is a 2014 documentary film directed by Zak Penn.
It is about the Atari video game burial excavation.
The film was released in 2014 by Microsoft on Xbox Live.
The film explores themes of video game, based on true story, landfill.